Contact

Mobile: +39 351 742 9828

E-mail: marcelofguermandi@gmail.com_

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/marcelo-fioresi-

guermandi/

Portfolio: https://mrnfg.github.io/

Skills

Git / GitHub / NPM

HTML / CSS / JavaScript

WordPress / WooCommerce

Figma / Adobe Design Programs

Bootstrap & Others CSS Frameworks

Design Best Practices & Accessibility

Problem Solving

Technical Support

Self-directed Learning

Languages

English - Fluent

Italian - Fluent

Portuguese - Native

Spanish - Limited Working Proficiency

Certifications

Photoshop for UX Design

Adobe Certified Associate InDesign

Become a User Experience Designer

Origamid Courses - HTML / CSS / JavaScript / UI/UX Design

Marcelo Fioresi Guermandi

Milan, Italy

Front-end Developer & UX/UI Designer

I'm a professional with more than five years of customer service and experience. Currently interested and motivated to work with Design and Development of Web and Mobile Applications as a Front-end Developer. I'm studying to become a Full Stack Developer. I'm looking for opportunities to enter the IT world. My area of work for the last few years has been another. But as everything changes, so have I and I've decided to look for my dream job.

Experience

GENERALI Italia - Claims Handler (Hybrid) december 2021 - december 2022 (1 year) Milan, Italy

AMAZON - Fulfillment Associate november 2020 - july 2021 (9 months) Castel San Giovanni, Italy

EZLINK Hotels - Tour Operator & Help Desk (Full-time/Remote)
december 2016 - march 2020 (3 year 4 months)
Maringá, Brazil

CINEFLIX Cinemas - Customer Service Attendant august 2015 - august 2016 (1 year) Maringá, Brazil

Education

UNINTER International University Center Systems Analysis and Development Bachelor Degree - 2017 - 2020

UEM Universidade Estadual de Maringá Philosophy

Unfinished College - 2014 - 2015